<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apps | CDRL</title>
    <link>/tags/apps/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tags/apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Apps</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Apps</title>
      <link>/tags/apps/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>KRSA App</title>
      <link>/project/projects_and_posters/krsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/projects_and_posters/krsa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kinome Random Sampling Analyzer, or &lt;strong&gt;KRSA&lt;/strong&gt;, is an R Shiny application that automates many of the steps required to analyze PamChip datasets, including peptide filtering, random sampling, heatmap generation, and kinase network generation. This new software makes analyzing kinome array datasets accessible and eliminates much of the human workload that the previous method required. More importantly, KRSA represents the results in a bigger biological context by visualizing altered kinome signaling networks instead of individual kinases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More info on the PamStation12 platform can be found here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://pamgene.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PamGene&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Package Website:&lt;br /&gt;
[&lt;a href=&#34;https://kalganem.github.io/KRSA/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://kalganem.github.io/KRSA/&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Access:&lt;br /&gt;
KRSA Shiny App GitHub Repository: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kalganem/KRSA_App&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
KRSA preprint is available here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.08.26.268581v1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;BioRxiv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaleidoscope App</title>
      <link>/project/projects_and_posters/kaleidoscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/projects_and_posters/kaleidoscope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kaleidoscope&lt;/strong&gt; is an interactive R Shiny web application that provides a platform for an easy access to biological databases and bioinformatics tools via a user-friendly interface that could be explored by researchers to test hypothesis in silico. Fully utilizing these robust bioinformatics tools and rich biological databases, interesting information can be obtained that could be very valuable to the field of biological psychiatry. The observations obtained from this platform could supplement existing hypotheses, spawn new ones and possibly direct future studies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
